{
  "duration": "10",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "All APIs of Node.JS are.",
      "options": [
        "Asynchronous",
        "Synchronous",
        "Both of the above.",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 1
    },

    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "Which of the following command will show all the modules installed locally.",
      "options": ["$ npm ls -g", "$ npm ls", "$ node ls -g", "$ node ls"],
      "correctOption": 2
    },

    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "Which of the following code gets length of a buffer buf?",
      "options": ["buf.length", "buf.size", "buf.length()", "buf.size()"],
      "correctOption": 1
    },

    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "Which method of fs module is used to write a file?",
      "options": [
        "fs.write(path, flags[, mode], callback)",
        "fs.writeFile(path, flags[, mode], callback)",
        "fs.writePath(path, flags[, mode], callback)",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 2
    },

    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about setInterval(cb, ms) global function?",
      "options": [
        "The setInterval(cb, ms) global function is used to run callback cb repeatedly after at least ms milliseconds.",
        "The setInterval(cb, ms) method returns an opaque value that represents the timer which can be used to clear the timer using the function clearInterval(t).",
        "Both of the above.",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 3
    },

    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "Which of the following is true about process global object?",
      "options": [
        "The process object is an instance of EventEmitter.",
        "process emits exit event when process is about to exit.",
        "process emits uncaughtException when when an exception bubbles all the way back to the event loop.",
        "All of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 4
    },

    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "Which of the following module is required for network specific operations?",
      "options": ["os module", "fs module", "net module", "None of the above."],
      "correctOption": 3
    },

    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "Which of the following method resolves an ip address to an array of hostnames?",
      "options": [
        "dns.reverse(ip, callback)",
        "dns.resolve(hostname[, rrtype], callback)",
        "dns.resolve4(hostname, callback)",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 1
    },

    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "Which of the following code can create a web server?",
      "options": [
        "http.createServer(callback)",
        "http.createWebServer(callback)",
        "http.createHTTPServer(callback)",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 1
    },

    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "Transform stream is a type of duplex stream.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correctOption": 1
    }
  ]
}
